<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All Over Earth</title>
    <description>Brandon and Gam are travelling All Over the Earth. We're documenting what we find, so stay tuned.</description>
    <link>https://allover.earth/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://allover.earth/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 15:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 15:46:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.5.0</generator>
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Vieques</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This trip we went to Vieques, another island on the North East of Puerto Rico.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove from San Juan to the Fajardo Ferry and then took the ferry to the island. It takes around 2 hours and was a little rougher (barf bags came out and babies were crying the whole time). But it was well worth it, as it was our favorite trip in Puerto Rico.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were much fewer tourists on Vieques and with only 10,000 locals split between the island’s 2 towns, it had a welcoming small-town vibe.  Everyone we met was very friendly and we had the opportunity to meet some very well travelled people while hitchhiking around the island.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/13-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/9-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time we got off the ferry it was already late afternoon, so we decided to head to the campground to get setup. We all took a taxi to Sun Bay campground ($10/night) and got settled in.  There were only around 4-5 other tents spread out over a large field, so it felt much more private than camping at Flamenco Beach.  Our campsite was right on the beach and could see the sand, palm trees, and water as soon as you got out of the tent in the morning. Throw in a Piña Colada and it would have made a great postcard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pro-tip: If you don’t want to pay the modest $10 to camp, you can just park right down the beach and camp (squat?) there. There’s no running water and you might get run over by one of the horses, but you can save your $$$ for that Piña Colada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/4-hori@big.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/10-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/14-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;post-image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/8-hori@big.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/2-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/3-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;post-image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/7-hori@big.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the morning, we walked to Esperanza, the town on the southern part of the island. We went to a bakery for breakfast and walked to Playa Negra (&lt;em&gt;Black Beach&lt;/em&gt;). During the way, we saw &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt; of horses. This island is well known for it’s wild horses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Playa Negra, we took a couple hours to swim and play in the black volcanic sand.  We got to see another family of wild horses on the beach and fed them some more peanuts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/1-ver@big.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/5-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/6-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next beach that we went to was Playa Caracas.  Our friend Maria is from Caracas, Venezuela so we had to go to get a picture with the sign.  I still haven’t found a Springfield Beach anywhere, but I’ll keep looking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/11-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/vieques/12-ver@small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a campfire on our last night and you know what? Off Spray is a propellant and works very well as a fire starter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also learned to hitch hike and it’s not too scary. The people who picked us up were very nice and had some interesting stories for us.  We might try it again in the future who knows…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://allover.earth/vieques</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://allover.earth/vieques</guid>
        
        
        <category>Beach</category>
        
        <category>PR</category>
        
        <category>Puerto Rico</category>
        
        <category>North America</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Culebra</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Puerto Rico has two nearby islands, Culebra and Vieques.  They’re both beautiful and they both have great campgrounds, beaches, snorkeling, and friendly people. We went on a camping trip to Culebra on a warm February weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We took an Uber from San Juan to the Fajardo Ferry terminal on a Friday afternoon.  We had originally planned to go to Vieques, but the Ferry to Culebra was about to leave and had some open seats, so we changed our plans (we saw Vieques another time, but that’s for another post).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-canal.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Canal in Culebra&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-ferry.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ferry at the Port in Culebra&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-boats.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Boats in harbor at culebra&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gam, myself, and the other 150 people onboard arrived in Culebra as it was getting dark outside.  We got in a Público (a shared taxi), along with an older couple who were also headed to the Playa Flamenco Campground.  A broken mirror and 20 minutes later, we got to the campground and setup camp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up the next morning as the sun was rising.  This was partly due to being excited, but sleeping on the sand and the dozens of wild roosters also had something to do with it ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-hen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chicken&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-zacco.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Zaccos Tacos&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We walked about 100 feet from our tent and were on the Playa Flamenco beach, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnn.com/2016/02/17/travel/tripadvisor-best-beaches-world-feat/&quot;&gt;the big tourist attraction&lt;/a&gt;.  It was breathtaking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-beach.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Playa Flamenco with sun rising&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;post-image-caption&quot;&gt;Playa Flamenco at sunrise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While waiting for our Taxi into town, an old hippie offered to give us a ride.  He said he comes to Culebra 3 months out of the year to go snorkeling/diving. He gave us some really good tips on where to go, so he is our new travel agent…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We picked up our Golf Cart and started to explore the island.  Our first stop was Playa Tamarindo, which is a feeding ground for sea turtles.  We snorkled out a ways and found 6 or 7 sea turtles.  They were absolutely massive, I really wish we would have gotten a picture, but we were too excited about finding them to get one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our next beach was Playa Zoni on the north east part of the island.  It only had about a dozen people at it, but was the most beautiful place I saw while in Puerto Rico.  The beach was pure white sand, private, and had a great view of neighboring islands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-relaxing.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture of Dinghy Dock restaurant&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-flower.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture of Dinghy Dock restaurant&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;post-image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-meow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture of Dinghy Dock restaurant&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had heard of a food truck parked on the highest point on the island that had seafood and a good view.  We trudged up the mountain in our golfcart only to find they were closed for President’s Day… that’s okay, it was still a beatiful view, even if we had to eat Cheezy Poofs for dinner ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-krabby-patty.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture of Dinghy Dock restaurant&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;post-image post-image--split&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-climbing.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Playa Punta de Soldado&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/culebra/culebra-tank.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Playa Flamenco with tank&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://allover.earth/culebra</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://allover.earth/culebra</guid>
        
        
        <category>Beach</category>
        
        <category>PR</category>
        
        <category>Puerto Rico</category>
        
        <category>North America</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
